(カカシ)まだか!?
(ヤマト)失敗だったんでしょうか？
Still nothing...
Could it have failed?
いや 手応えは 確かにあった。
No, there definitely was an impact.
(いの)でも 何も起こらないわ
ヒナタ 何か見えないの？
But nothing's happening...
Hinata, can you see anything?
(ヒナタ)え ええ
白眼でも そこまでは。
N-No... Not even with my Byakugan...
(サクラ)ナルトは
ナルトは戻ってこないの？
Naruto...Naruto won't come back?
Did it reach Naruto?
《ナルトたちのところまで
届かなかったのか？
しかも 三尾を
目覚めさせてしまったらしい》
Furthermore, it seems to have awakened
the Three-Tails.
シズネ！
Shizune!
(シズネ)封印班
三尾出現に備えるわよ！
Sealing team!
Standby for the Three-Tails!
(３人)はい！
サイ！
Right!
Sai!
幽鬼丸を 安全なところに頼む。
(サイ)はい。
Take Yuukimaru to a safe place.
Right!
行こう。
- Let's go.
- No!
(幽鬼丸)イヤだ 紅蓮さんが
帰ってくるまで ここにいる！
I'm staying here until Guren returns!
(サクラ)きっと大丈夫。
え？
I'm sure she's all right.
Huh?
みんな ナルトのことを思ってるから。
We're all thinking of Naruto,
that's why he'll return here.
ナルトは ここに帰ってくる。
あなたが思ってれば
そこに紅蓮も帰ってくるわ 必ず。
If you think of her, Guren will return too.
No doubt about it.
さあ。
Now then...
うん。
Okay.
Go!
いけ！
結界四方封陣 縛の術式をとる。
We will begin
the Four-Corner Sealing Jutsu.
結界四方封陣 縛！
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier...
Bind!
問題は ここからだな。
The challenge starts now...
Until the Sealing team has
the Three-Tails,
封印班が三尾を捕らえるまで
オレたちで抑えることになるが。
it's up to us to suppress it.
さて 三尾相手に
ボクの木遁が どこまで通じますか。
Now then, we'll see just how well
my Wood Style works
against the Three-Tails.
ま やれるだけ やるっきゃないね。
All we can do is try...
Counterattack of
the Curse Mark
ここで待とう いいね？
We'll wait here. All right?
うん ふ～。
Okay.
飲んで 疲れがとれる。
え？
Drink... It will ease your fatigue.
お兄さん わかるんだ
ボクの思ってること。
You can tell what I'm thinking...
みんなには 空気が読めないって
言われるけど。
Everyone tells me that
I can't read their moods.
そんなことないよ きっと。
I doubt that. Really...
はあ フフ。
(鬼鳳)魔煙丸！
Dark Smoke Sphere
Stay hidden, okay?
隠れているんだ いいね。
うん。
Okay.
Water Shield Shot!
(濡羅吏)粘水塊！
ヘッ！
(鬼霧)フフフフッ…。
かくれんぼかい？
Hide-and-seek, eh?
I've come for you, laddie.
お迎えにあがったぜ お坊ちゃん。
I've been able to determine
Yuukimaru's potential
(カブト)すでに 幽鬼丸の能力の
可能性と限界は確かめられた。
and the limit of his power.
However, the Hidden Leaf are trying
to seal the Three-Tails once again...
しかし 木ノ葉のヤツら また
三尾を封印しようというのか。
もし 万が一にも木ノ葉が➡
If by any chance, they are successful
in sealing the Three-Tails...
三尾の封印に
成功してしまったら…。
((大蛇丸 : サスケ君が必要なスキルを
手に入れさえすれば➡
When Sasuke achieves
the skills he needs...
The time for my reanimation will be near.
転生の時期も近いわ。
When that happens,
そうなれば
暁も 木ノ葉も邪魔なだけ。
both the Akatsuki and Leaf Village
will be a hindrance.
Our current operation is preparation
for when that happens.
(今度の作戦は
そのときのための準備))
三尾の力を暁に
利用される心配はなくなるが。
We won't have to worry about
the Akatsuki using
the power of the Three Tails, but...
大蛇丸様の未来戦略に
大きな変更を余儀なくされる。
It will force a big change
in Lord Orochimaru's future strategy.
それは 防がなければ。
We must avoid that...
これを使えば
幽鬼丸を失うかもしれない。
If I use this, we may lose Yuukimaru...
However, rather than lose
the Three-Tails...
しかし三尾そのものを失うよりは。
例え 幽鬼丸を
失ってもかまうものか。
Never mind...if I lose Yuukimaru!
幽鬼丸の最後の
力を使って 三尾を暴れさせ➡
I'll use Yuukimaru's remaining power
to make the Three-Tails go wild,
木ノ葉の忍どもを蹴散らしてやる。
and destroy the Leaf Ninja...!
カブトは？
(鱗児)フン。
Where's Kabuto...?
Huh, I heard everything.
オレが すべて聞いておいた。
ウフフ…！
メガネ君はいないんだ。
So Four-Eyes isn't here?
フッ！ それじゃあ
オレたちに命令するヤツは➡
So there's no one to give us orders...
いねえってわけだねぇ！
あ？
オレたちゃ 昔の
オレたちじゃねえってことさ。
We're not the same as before.
There's no need to hang
around you anymore...
もう アンタとつるむ必要も
なくなっちゃったし。
Well, it looks that way...
ま そういうことだ。
You guys are so easygoing.
いい気なもんだぜ。
何!?
What...?
You guys are just cast-offs...
pawns who are no longer useful.
所詮 テメエらは
利用されてなんぼの捨て駒だ。
And you don't even know that
I've got you in a vital spot.
まんまと急所を
握られてるってのに➡
気づきもしねえってか!?
クッ！
Say that again!
言わせておきゃ！
アンタもう➡
You're not one of us anymore!
オレたちの仲間じゃねえ！
ここで➡
Want to settle it now?
始末してやってもいいのよ。
始末？
Settle?
フッ フフフフ… アハハハ…！
なんだ 何がおかしい！
What?! What's so funny?!
クククク… そろそろのはずだぜ！
It's about time!
What...?! My body feels strange...
なんだか 体が変だよ！
ふ 震えが止まらねえ！
I can't stop shaking...
おい どうした!?
Hey, what's happening?!
グワッ！ ああっ!!
バカめ!!
Fools!
力を得るためには
リスクが伴うと知れ！
You should know that
there's a risk to attaining power!
I heard your power has
some side effects!
お前たちの力には
副作用があるって話だぜ！
ふ 副作用だぁ!?
そうさ。
Side effects...?!
Yeah...
And left alone, it will eat you up
from the inside out.
放っときゃ 体の内部から
崩れちまうんだとさ！
N-No... I don't want that to happen!
い いやよ！ そんなの!!
そ そんな… 死にたくねえ！
N-No way... I don't want to die!
フンッ！ 定期的に
カブトから薬をもらわねえと➡
Unless you get the drug from Kabuto
before the time limit,
you'll destroy yourselves
with your own power!
お前たちは お前たち自身の力で
破滅するんだよ！
カブトから預かっている！
Kabuto entrusted the drug to me.
If you say you won't betray
Lord Orochimaru,
大蛇丸様を
裏切らないっていうんなら➡
I just may give it to you.
くれてやるがな！
All right. I swear my loyalty.
わかった… 忠誠を誓う。
H-Hurry...give me the drug.
は 早く薬を！
Know this! No matter how hard you try,
思い知れ！ お前たちは
どう足掻いたって➡
you will never be able to escape
Lord Orochimaru's grasp.
大蛇丸様の掌の上からは
逃げられないんだよ！
カブトが言っていた。
Kabuto said this...
We've stopped
the Three-Tails' movements.
三尾の動きを止めた➡
And he wants to see that
power once more.
あの力をもう一度
見せてほしいってな。
No!
いやだ！
When I take that medicine,
my head feels like it's going to burst...
あの薬を飲むと
頭が割れるように痛くなる。
Shut up! You will not refuse!
黙れ！ 拒むことは許さない！
Guren hasn't returned yet!
And maybe, she'll never return!
まだ紅蓮は
戻ってきていない。
永遠に戻らないかも
しれないんだぞ!?
Do you want that?!
それでもいいのか!?
いやだ…。
No... No!
いやだよぉ！
だったら➡
Then stop being fussy and do as I say!
つべこべ言わず
オレの言うとおりにしろ!!
う うん。 もう一度…。
O-Okay... One more time.
Just one more time...
本当に もう一度だけだよ。
ああ！ それで最後だ！
Yeah... this is the last time.
くるか。
Here it comes...
おっ！
(カカシ)サイの使いか。
Is that from Sai?
どうやら 紅蓮の仲間の忍が
パワーアップし サイを襲ったらしい。
It seems Guren's fellow Ninja have
powered up and attacked Sai.
えっ!?
キバたちからの連絡は？
Huh?!
Any word from Kiba and the rest?
No, not yet.
いえ まだ…。
(シノ)まさか…。
No way...
(赤丸)バウ…。
赤丸 助かったぜ。
Akamaru, you saved me...
お前の機転で
地面に潜ってなきゃ オレたち…。
If we hadn't hidden underground
due to your quick thinking...
ク～ン…。
リー… テンテン！
Lee... Tenten...?
まさか アイツら…。
They couldn't have...!
すまん 赤丸… 大丈夫だ。
Thank you, Akamaru... I'm okay.
(キバ)お前ら 無事だったんだな！
You're all okay.
(テンテン)全然 無事じゃないわよ。
Not at all.
If I didn't summon a protection Wall
from my scroll,
巻物から防御壁を
呼び出してなきゃ やられてたわ。
we'd have been goners...
リーのヤツ 闇雲に突っ込んでいくし。
Lee was no help, rushing in like that...
(リー)くっ… 悔しいです…。
I-I'm mortified...
After Guy Sensei often warned me
that pride is a Ninja's enemy...
ガイ先生からも 常々 慢心は
忍者の敵といわれていたのに…。
まさか アイツらが
あんなにやるとはね。
I didn't expect it...
That they'd be so strong.
(キバ)いや。
No...
That transformation isn't normal.
We must notify everyone!
あの変わりようは
ただごとじゃねえ。
早いとこ みんなに知らせねえと。
ええ。
Yes...
(シノ)この霧…。
This fog... We're already in their trap...
オレたちは すでに
ヤツらの術中にいる。
封印班を守るんだ。
はい！
Protect the Sealing team!
Right!
魔煙丸！
Dark Smoke Sphere!
粘水塊！
Water Shield Shot!
ヤマト！
はい。
- Yamato!
- Right!
Wood Style: Giant Forest!
木遁 樹界壁！
この… 邪魔しやがって!!
Why you--! Getting in the way!
Wood Style: Giant Forest Jutsu!
木遁 大樹林の術！
くっ…。
寄壊蟲！
Parasitic Insect!
ん!? なに？
What? Hey, stop!
ちょっと！ イヤだ！ イヤー!!
Nooo!
おりゃ!!
ぐはっ！
What's wrong, Akamaru?!
どうした？ 赤丸！
みんな止まれ！ 様子が変だ！
Everyone, stop!
Something's strange here.
The enemy?!
敵ですか!?
いや これは…。
No... This is...
(テンテン)どう見ても
敵ではなさそうね。
It doesn't look like the enemy at all...
Tenten! You can tell
what Akamaru is feeling?!
(リー)テンテン 赤丸君の気持が
読めるんですか!?
あっ！ サイ!!
Sai!
This is the Three-Tails' fog...
ほう… この霧は 三尾の。
まだ封印は 完了していないな。
The sealing isn't complete yet.
あっ… 来るよ！
アイツが来る！
It's coming...! It's coming!
Gather your Chakra!
チャクラを集中させて！
はい！
- Yes!
- Right!
了解！
しゃ～んなろ～！
Cha!
来たか！
Here it comes!
(鱗児)飲むんだ 幽鬼丸！
えっ！
Swallow it, Yuukimaru.
Huh?!
Swallow all of it!
You want Guren to return, don't you?
全部 飲むんだ！
紅蓮に帰ってきてほしいんだろ？
わかった！ ボクやるよ！
Okay, I'll do it.
紅蓮さんのいるところが
ボクの帰る場所だから。
Because the place
I'll return to is where Guren is...
(紅蓮)うっ あっ…。
戻れたのか…。
I made it back...
うっ あっ…。
Feeling pain means I'm still alive.
痛いってことは
まだ生きてるってことだな。
あっ！
Naruto...
(紅蓮)ナルト…。
起きろ！ ナルト！
うっ…。
Wake up! Naruto!
Yuukimaru... you're okay?
幽鬼丸… 無事だったか？
This is no time to babble in your sleep!
寝ぼけている場合じゃないだろ！
ん？
うわっ！
オレたち 戻れたのか？
ああ。
We made it back...?
Yeah...
幽鬼丸… 幽鬼丸！ どこだ!?
Yuukimaru... Where's Yuukimaru?!
(鬼霧)フフフフッ… ハハハハ！
煙重分身。
Multi-Smoke Clone.
No... Stop!
イヤ～ やめて！
あぁ あぁ～！
ウフフフフフ。
くすぐった～い。
なに!?
It tickles...
What?!
Oh dear... Your cute little bugs
are shapeless now.
あらあら あなたの
かわいい蟲さんたちも形無しね。
それじゃあ 本番いくわよ
はっ！
Well, now for the main show.
Here I come!
うっ！
フフ。
おもしれえ
こいつはいただきだ！
This is interesting...
I'm taking this!
Arise Smoke Dragon!
出でよ 煙龍！
あっ！ あ あ…。
《サイが伝えてきたとおり➡
Like Sai reported...
以前のコイツらとは
まるで別人だな》
they're totally different from before.
うぅ…！
うっ！
Sh-Shizune Senpai...!
シズネ先輩！
いのは限界か しかし…。
Ino has reached her limit... But...
いの なんとか持ち堪えて！
Ino! Just hang in there!
Shizune...
No way! Not that power again!
Yuukimaru!
Yuukimaru may not forgive me
when he finds out...the whole truth.
Are you still mulling over that?
≪(カツユ)シズネ様…。
I'm prepared to protect Yuukimaru, but...
If I were you, I'd keep thinking of him!
Even if I'm despised, or rejected...
or resented!
Whether he thinks that
I'm the place to return to or not...
うわぁ～!!
has nothing to do with it!
Yeah, you're right!
I'll become the fool too...just like you.
まさか また あの力を？
幽鬼丸！
Next time:
"Memory of Guilt"
昆虫採集が趣味だという
油女シノ君。
YAMATO'S ROOM
Shino Aburame,
who loves to collect insects...
今日のお客様です。
is our guest today.
さっそくですが シノ君は
木ノ葉でも有数の一族である➡
Getting right to the point...
Shino, you're a member of the prominent
Aburame family in Leaf Village,
油女一族のご出身で
いつもクールにきめてるけど➡
and you're always calm and cool.
Is the rest of your family like you?
ご家族の皆さんも
そうなんですか？
寡黙であること すなわち…。
Silence. Namely...
なるほど 寡黙は つまり
体内に宿している蟲たちとの➡
I see. Silence signifies that
you are communicating
対話を意味すると
そういうことですね。
with the insects you host
inside your bodies?
ああ。
生まれたときから➡
Yes...
I understand that in the Aburame family,
なにか特別なことを
されるそうですが。
you do something special from
the time you are born?
それは 一族の秘術として…。
That is a secret family Jutsu...
体の中に蟲を寄生させて➡
From the time you are born,
you host insects inside your body,
ご自身のチャクラを与えることで
共存していると➡
sustain them with your Chakra,
and co-exist.
簡単に言えば
こういうことですね。
ああ。
Is that a simple way of putting it?
Yes...
その蟲たちを使って 追尾 治癒
分身などを行う秘伝術こそが➡
And you use the insects in
your secret Jutsu to do things
like tracking, healing and cloning.
秘術なんですね。
ああ。
And that is your secret family Jutsu,
is that correct?
Yes...
ちょっと見せてもらえません？
ここで!?
Can you demonstrate for us?
Here...?
できなければ結構ですけど。
It's okay if you can't.
時間がないので
ちゃっちゃと やってください。
We're running out of time,
so please do it quickly.
では…。
おっと 時間です。
今日のお客様 油女シノ君でした。
(シノ)もう終わり…。